A Guide to the Louise Wright Bailey Genealogical Collection
Roanoke Public Libraries
- (Box 1)
  - Records arranged alphabetically by geographical location and type of record thereunder. Please note that census records listed during non-census years were generated from substitute census records, such as tithables and personal property tax records. (Box 11 of 12)
    - Virginia: Shenandoah County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1782-1804 (Folder 51)
    - Virginia: Shenandoah County: Wills/Deeds, 1798-1812 and 1826-1827 (Folder 52)
    - Virginia: Smyth County: Census, 1840-1900 (Folder 53)
    - Virginia: Smyth County: Marriages, 1831-1850 (Folder 54)
    - Virginia: Spotsylvania to Sussex County: Census, various years (Folder 55)
    - Virginia: Stafford County: Deed Abstracts, 1722-1728 (Folder 56)
    - Virginia: Surry County: Marriages, 1679-1790 (Folder 57)
    - Virginia: Sussex County: Marriages, 1754-1783 (Folder 58)
    - Virginia: Tazewell County: Census, 1810-1850 (Folder 59)
    - Virginia: Tazewell County: Census, 1860-1880 (Folder 60)
    - Virginia: Tazewell County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1801-1842 (Folder 61)
    - Virginia: Unknown County: Inventory of the Estate of William Remine, 10 September 1870 (Folder 62)
    - Virginia: Washington County (Folder 63)
    - Virginia: Washington County: Census, 1810-1900 (Folder 64)
    - Virginia: Washington County: Deeds of George Wright, 1888 and 1902 (Folder 65)
    - Virginia: Washington County: Miscellaneous (Folder 66)
    - Virginia: Warren to Westmoreland County: Census, various years (Folder 67)
    - Virginia: Wise County: Census, 1860 (Folder 68)
    - Virginia: Wise County: Marriages, 1856-1858 (Folder 69)
    - Virginia: Wythe County: Baptisms, 1779-1920 (Folder 70)
    - Virginia: Wythe County: Indenture for Thomas and Katherine Dunn, et. al., 20 September 1842 (Folder 71)
    - Virginia: Wythe County: Inventory of the Estate of Michael Creagar, 1 June 1827 (Folder 72)
    - Virginia: Wythe County: Marriages, 1790-1800 (Folder 73)
    - Virginia: Wythe to York County: Census, various years (Folder 74)
    - Virginia: York County: Parish Registers, 1648-1789 (Folder 75)
    - Washington: Census, various years (Folder 76)
    - West Virginia: Boone to Mercer County: Census, 1880 (Folder 77)
    - West Virginia: Cabell County: Census, 1820, 1830 and 1850 (Folder 78)
    - West Virginia: Cabell County: Marriages, 1810-1851 (Folder 79)
    - West Virginia: Cabell County: Miscellaneous (Folder 80)
    - West Virginia: Fayette County: Census, 1840-1850 (Folder 81)
    - West Virginia: Greenbrier County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 82)
    - West Virginia: Greenbrier County: Court Orders, 1780-1850 (Folder 83)
    - West Virginia: Greenbrier County: Marriages, 1781-1849 (Folder 84)
    - West Virginia: Hampshire County: Census, 1790-1850 (Folder 85)
    - West Virginia: Hardy County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 86)
    - West Virginia: Harrison County: Census, 1782, 1811-1850 (Folder 87)
    - West Virginia: Jackson County: Census. 1840-1840 (Folder 88)
    - West Virginia: Jefferson County: Census, 1810-1860 (Folder 89)
    - West Virginia: Kanawha County: Census, 1810-1860 (Folder 90)
    - West Virginia: Kanawha County: Marriages, 1792-1869 (Folder 91)
    - West Virginia: Lewis County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 92)
    - West Virginia: Logan County: Census, 1840-1850 (Folder 93)
    - West Virginia: McDowell County: Census, 1860-1870 (Folder 94)
    - West Virginia: Madison County: Census, 1810, 1820 and 1850 (Folder 95)
    - West Virginia: Mason County: Census, 1820-1880 (Folder 96)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Births, 1853-1904 (Folder 97)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census, 1840 (Folder 98)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census, 1850 (Folder 99)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census, 1860 (Folder 100)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census, 1870 (Folder 101)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census, 1880 (Folder 102)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Census 1900 (Folder 103)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Deaths, 1853-1905 (Folder 104)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Marriages, 1853-1890 (Folder 105)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Marriages, 1853-1901 (Folder 106)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1837-1849 (Folder 107)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County: Wills/Deeds, 1863-1949 (Folder 108)
    - West Virginia: Monongalia County: Census: 1790-1850 (Folder 109)
    - West Virginia: Monroe County: Census, 1840-1860 (Folder 110)
    - West Virginia: Monroe County: Land Grants from Dyer’s Index, 1800-1862 (Folder 111)
    - West Virginia: Monroe to Wyoming County: Census, various years (Folder 112)
    - West Virginia: Ohio County: Census, 1810-1850 (Folder 113)
    - West Virginia: Pendleton County: Census, 1810 and 1830 (Folder 114)
    - West Virginia: Putnam County: Census, 1850 (Folder 115)
    - West Virginia: Raleigh County: Census, 1850-1870 (Folder 116)
    - West Virginia: Randolph County: Census, 1850 (Folder 117)
    - West Virginia: Tyler County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 118)
    - West Virginia: Wayne County: Census, 1850-1860 (Folder 119)
    - West Virginia: Wirt County: Census, 1850-1860 (Folder 120)
    - West Virginia: Wood County: Census, 1810-1860 (Folder 121)
    - West Virginia: Wyoming County: Census, 1850-1860 (Folder 122)
    - Research: Draft – “Straley Family of Giles County, Virginia” by Louise Bailey (Folder 123)
    - Research: Thesis – “The Quality of the Opposition” by Harry Bailey (Folder 124)
    - Research: “Vaughts of Virginia” by Louise Bailey (Folder 125)
    - Wedding Announcements (Folder 126)
  - 35 spiral-bound notebooks with source citations for Bailey research (Box 12 of 12)